Contact

banasmita09@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/banasmita-das-364121158 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

WordPress

creator

Facebook

Languages

Assamese

Hindi

English

Certifications

Bridge Design

Creator Course

Basics of IT, Basics of Computer Hardware& Networking ,Operating System: DOS/Windows XP ,Packages: MS-Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint), Software tools: DTP (English), Adobe Photoshop

Banasmita Das

Support Executive | Digital Creator

Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

Summary

I am fascinated by digital marketing.

I have completed my B. Tech in Civil Engineering at Central Institute of Technology, Kokrajhar.

After finishing my B. Tech, I have worked for one one-year as an Administrative Assistant at Montessori Training Institute. By then pursued my M. Tech in Environmental & Management at Pondicherry University. Also, I have split my educational focus into Digital Marketing and Excel to gain more knowledge

Experience

eMudhra
Support executive
July 2023 - Present (4 months)
Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

Guarented
Digital Marketing Executive
June 2023 - June 2023 (1 month)
Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

Montessori Teacher Training Institute Administrative Assistant August 2020 - August 2021 (1 year 1 month) Guwahati, Assam, India

Education

Pondicherry University

Master of Technology - MTech, Environmental Engineering and management · (2021 - May 2023)

Central Institute of Technology, Kokrajhar

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Civil Engineering · (August 2021)

Potential & Concept Education, Guwahati

Rajdhani Public School

Pragjyotish English Medium High School